Tom Miller papers, 1852-2003 (Bulk 1950-2003)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Publications by Tom Miller
  - Subseries 3: Books and Manuscripts
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Peamey, John R., 1989, No date (Box 32, Folder 83)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Peixotto, Ernest, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 84)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Polkinhorn, Harry, No date (Box 32, Folder 85)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Reavis, Dick J., 1987, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 86)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Rechy, John, 1959, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 87)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Riding, Alan, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 88)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Robinson, Cecil, 1977,1987 (Box 32, Folder 89)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Rocard, Marcienne, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 90)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Rochlin, Harriet, 1981, No date (Box 32, Folder 91)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Rodriguez, Juan Holguin, 1984, No date (Box 32, Folder 92)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Rohter, Larry, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 93)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Romo, Ricardo, 1987, No date (Box 32, Folder 94)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Rossi, Alejandro, No date (Box 32, Folder 95)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Sanowsky, Roland, No date (Box 32, Folder 96)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Samora, Julian, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 97)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Sanmiguel, Rosario, No date (Box 32, Folder 98)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Santos, John Phillip, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 99)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Segal, Aaron, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 100)
    - Writing on the Edge-Submissions -Shelton, Gilbert, No date (Box 32, Folder 101)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Simpich, Fredricj, 1920, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 102)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Singer, Mark, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 103)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -South, Marshall, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 104)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Theroux, Paul, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 105)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Urrea, Luis Alberto, No date (Box 32, Folder 106)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -U.S.-Mexico Border Treaties, 1848, 1853 (Box 32, Folder 107)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Valdes, Gina, No date (Box 32, Folder 108)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Van Dyke, John, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 109)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Vasconcelos, Jose, No date (Box 32, Folder 110)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Villareal, Jose Antonio, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 111)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Walker, Fred, No date (Box 32, Folder 112)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Waters, Frank, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 113)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -West, John O., 1988 (Box 32, Folder 114)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -White, Stewart Edward, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 115)
    - Writing on the Edge -Submissions -Zeta Acosta, Oscar, No date (Box 32, Folder 116)
- Series II: Research Files
  - Subseries 1: General Research Files
    - Research Files -General -Alarma! 1986, No date (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -General -Alcoholic Drinks 1967, No date (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -General -Alinnsky, Saul, 1983-1984, No date (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -General -APA/CIA, 1964-1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -General -Article Manuscripts, 1968-1982, No date (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -General -Arizona Crucification, No date (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Research Files -General -Arizona Ku Klux Klan, 1973-1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Research Files -General -Authors Guild Bulletin, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Research Files -General -Author's Income, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Research Files -General -Babies/Border, 1975-1982, No date (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Research Files -General -Baseball, 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Research Files -General -Big Bend Texas, 1975-1998, No date (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Research Files -General -Bighorn Sheep, 1977-1979, No date (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Research Files -General -Bisbee Brew, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Research Files -General -Blue Ridge Parkway, 1983, No date (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Research Files -General -Border, 1971-2001 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Research Files -General -Border Health, 1980-1983, No date (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Research Files -General -Border Music, 1975-1978, No date (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Research Files -General -Border Radio Series, No date (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Research Files -General -Border Smuggling/Drugs (Includes Photographs), 1975-2001, No date (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Research Files -General -Border WWI, 1983, No date (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Research Files -General -Border and Travel, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Research Files -General -Borderland Violence -Miscellaneous Materials, 1978-1980, No date (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Research Files -General -Borderland Violence -Newspaper Clippings, 1972-2001, No date (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Research Files -General -Borderfield State Park, 1978-1987, No date (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Research Files -General -Border Town Cafes, 1979-1990, No date (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Research Files -General -Border que Border, 1983-1990, No date (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Research Files -General -Bowling, 1991-1994, No date (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Research Files -General -Brownsville/Matamores, 1977-1993, No date (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Research Files -General -Brown Rice Riots, 1970-1971, No date (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Research Files -General -Bumper Stickers, No date (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Research Files -General -California Border Towns, 1992, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Research Files -General -Candelilla Wax, 1970-1984, No date (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Research Files -General -Casa Grande Football Team, 1982-1989 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Research Files -General -Chicken Scratch Music/Canyon Records, 1975-1997, No date (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Research Files -General -Chinavajo, 1989, No date (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Research Files -General -Cochise Country Jewish Cemetery, 1992-2000, No date (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Research Files -General -Cockfighting, 1989-2000, No date (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Research Files -General -Company Towns, 1981-1983, No date (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Research Files -General -Correspondence -Magazines, 1974-1983, No date (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Research Files -General -Culbert, Pat -Maya Enter History, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Research Files -General -Denver Candy (Includes Photographs), 1922-1996 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Research Files -General -Desert, 1896-1987 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Research Files -General -DeSoto, Hernado, 1994-1996, No date (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Research Files -General -Eagle Pass -Del Rio/Piedra Negras -Cd. Acuna, 1976-1981, No date (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Research Files -General -Drugs, 1993-1997 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Research Files -General -EAU de Saguaro, No date (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Research Files -General -Earp, Wyatt, 1988, No date (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Research Files -General -Eco Raiders (Earth First!) -Miscellaneous (Includes Photographs), 1972-1973, No date (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Research Files -General -Eco Raiders (Earth First!) -Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1992, No date (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -General -Ecuador, 1918-1998, No date (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -General -Electronic Rights, 1993-1996, No date (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -General -El Paso/Juarez, 1885-1999 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -General -English Language, 1991-1997 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -General -Ex-Patriots, 1982-1984 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Research Files -General -Four Corners, 1985-1989, No date (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Research Files -General -Fox, Karen Lee, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Research Files -General -Freedom of Information Act -Personal, 1975-1997, No date (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Research Files -General -Fugate, Paul, 1981, No date (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Research Files -General -Garcia, Jesus, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Research Files -General -Garreau, Joel, No date (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Research Files -General -Goldwater, Barry -Correspondence, 1978-1986 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Research Files -General -Guanajuato, No date (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Research Files -General -Guatemalan Refugee Camps/Chiapas, 1983-1984, No date (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Research Files -General -Hall, Raymond, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Research Files -General -Hawke, George, 2001, No date (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Research Files -General -Hayes, Ira, 1976-1998 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Research Files -General -Hopi Dictionary, 1989-1990, No date (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Research Files -General -Houser, John, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Research Files -General -Immigrants, 1991-2001 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Research Files -General -Indians -South America, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Research Files -General -IRE/Bolles (Pt.1), 1977 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Research Files -General -IRE/Bolles (Pt.2), 1977-1986, No date (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Research Files -General -Japanese Internment Arizona, 1984-1989 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Research Files -General -Jews (Includes Photographs), 1984-2000, No date (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Research Files -General -Jews -Latin America, 1941-1999, No date (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Research Files -General -Jimenez, Luis, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Research Files -General -Journalism, 1982-2001 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Research Files -General -Judge Crater, 1967-1990, No date (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Research Files -General -Kickapoo Indians, 1977-1985, No date (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Research Files -General -Kino Mission Tour, 1981-1989, No date (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Research Files -General -Kleindienst, Richard, 1982-1987, No date (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Research Files -General -Knobel, Gail, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Research Files -General -Krausman, Pat 1984 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Research Files -General -Kopkind, Andrew, 1970-1995 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Research Files -General -Lands End, 1993-1999, No date (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Research Files -General -Language, 1963-2000, No date (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Research Files -General -Latin America -Borders, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Research Files -General -Library of Congress Catalog, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Research Files -General -Laredo, Texas, 1986-2001, No date (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Research Files -General -Latin American, Afro, 1989-1994 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Research Files -General -Latin American Art, 1990-2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -General -Latino Film, 1980-1993, No date (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -General -Lefty Stuff, 1968-1978, No date (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -General -Letters of Introduction, 1994-2000 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -General -Literary Life, 1991-2001, No dates (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -General -Lochiel -Border, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Research Files -General -Lopez, Jimmy 1982 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Research Files -General -Lottery, No date (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Research Files -General -Maquiladoras, 1986-2001, No date (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Research Files -General -Ludlow Massacre, 1966-1983, No date (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Research Files -General -Mast General Store, 1930-1994, No date (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Research Files -General -Mavrides, Paul, 1995, No date (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Research Files -General -Mexico Miscellaneous Materials, 1909-1997, No date (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Research Files -General -Marks of Birth, 1994, No date (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Research Files -General -"Me 'n Henry", 1985-2000, No date (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Research Files -General -Mechanics -Novel, 1982, No date (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Research Files -General -Mendoza, Elfego, No date (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Research Files -General -Mexicali/Calexico, 1979, No date (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Research Files -General -Mexico City, 1980-1994 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Research Files -General -Mexico -Ecology, 1984-1988 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Research Files -General -Mexico -Music, 1988-1999 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Research Files -General -Mexico -Trains, 1963-1993, No date (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Research Files -General -Mexican Arts and Crafts, 1993-1998, No date (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Research Files -General -Mexican Elections, 1993, No date (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Research Files -General -Museum of Intervention, 1986-1988, No date (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Research Files -General -Miami, 1990-1992, No date (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Research Files -General -Miscellaneous, 1962-1992, No date (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Research Files -General -Milagro Beanfield War (Includes Photographs), 1986, No date (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Research Files -General -Mining Towns, 1980-1999, No date (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Research Files -General -Monroy, Oscar, 1978-1995, No date (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Research Files -General -MTV Professor 1986 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Research Files -General -Murals, 1987-1997, No date (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Research Files -General -MUSE, 1996-1998 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Research Files -General -Music, 1969-2000 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Research Files -General -National Public Radio, 1997-1999, No date (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Research Files -General -Navajo, 1983, No date (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Research Files -General -New Mexico, 1993-2001, No date (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Research Files -General -New Mexico Border Towns, 1978-1993, No date (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Research Files -General -New Times, 1973-2003 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Research Files -General -New York Times Corrections, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Research Files -General -North South Productions, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Research Files -General -Noshirani, Zarir, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Research Files -General -Obituaries, 1995-2001 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Research Files -General -Ochs, Phil -Folk Singer, 1973-1997, No date (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Research Files -General -Olympics in Atlanta, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Research Files -General -Open Pit Mine, No date (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Research Files -General -Parrot Smuggling, 1979-1990, No date (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Research Files -General -Pellicer, Ana, 1986-1989, No date (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Research Files -General -Phoenix, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Research Files -General -Perez, Yuliana (Yara), 1987-2001, No date (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Research Files -General -Peru, 1982-1985, No date (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -General -Photography, 1971-2001, No date (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -General -Photography -Kufeld Book, 1993, No date (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -General -Pinacates (Pt.1), 1946-2000, No date (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -General -Pinacates (Pt.2) (Includes Photographs), 1946-2000, No date (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -General -Plagiarism, 1990-1999, No date (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Research Files -General -Polacios, Francisco, 1969-2000, No date (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Research Files -General -Political Convention and Inaugurations, 1961-1968, No date (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Research Files -General -Postcards (Includes Sterographs), 1899-2000, No date (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Research Files -General -Publishing, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Research Files -General -Rabbi, 2000, No date (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Research Files -General -Rice, Donna, 1987-1999 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Research Files -General -Rio Grande, 1982-1999, No date (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Research Files -General -Rio Grande City, Texas, 1976-1985, No date (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Research Files -General -Rio Rico USA, 1976-1980, No date (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Research Files -General -Rodent Cookbook, 1964-1985, No date (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Research Files -General -Rodin Crater, 1969-1984, No date (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Research Files -General -Rock and Plane Crashes, 1959-1974, No date (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Research Files -General -Rolling Stone (Includes Photographs), 1967-1977, No date (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Research Files -General -Rosa's Cantina (Includes Photographs), 1966-1994, No date (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Research Files -General -Route 66, 1984-1985, No date (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Research Files -General -Rubin, J.R., 1970-1995, No date (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Research Files -General -"Run for the Border", 1989, No date (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Research Files -General -Saddles (Includes Photographs), 1973-1999, No date (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Research Files -General -Salvadorian Desert Trek, 1980-1981, No date (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Research Files -General -Sanctuary Break-ins, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Research Files -General -Sanders, Ed, 1976, No date (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Research Files -General -Santa Fe Style, 1987-1990, No date (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Research Files -General -Sandy Spring Friends School, 1971-1990, No date (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -General -Scalan's Guerrilla War in the U.S. 1971 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -General -Schmid (Smitty), Charles, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -General -70s Stuff, 1980, No date (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -General -Sex, No date (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -General -Sharpe, Luis, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Research Files -General -Sinohi, Joe J.R., 1977-1980, No date (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Research Files -General -Sierra Club -Trail Calendar, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Research Files -General -60s Stuff, 1969-2000, No date (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Research Files -General -Sky Hero, 1987-1988, No date (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Research Files -General -Skywriting, 1994, No date (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Research Files -General -Sonoyta/Lukeville, 1977-1993, No date (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Research Files -General -Sonora, Mexico, 1998, No date (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Research Files -General -South America, 1986-2000 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Research Files -General -Spinoza, 1989, No date (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Research Files -General -Starsky, Morris, 1975,1989 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Research Files -General -Stavans, Ilan, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Research Files -General -Stirling, Dickson, No date (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Research Files -General -Texaco -CEPE, 1970-1984, No date (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Research Files -General -Texas Border Towns, 1990-2001, No date (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Research Files -General -Third World, 1974-1985, No date (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Research Files -General -Tigua Indians, 1980, No date (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Research Files -General -Tijuana, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Research Files -General -Tohono O'Odham, 1977-1990 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Research Files -General -Tombstone, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Research Files -General -Translations, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Research Files -General -Trinity Site, 1974-2000, No date (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Research Files -General -Tucson, 1971-2000, No date (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Research Files -General -Tucson vs. Phoenix, 1987, No date (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Research Files -General -Translations, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Research Files -General -UFW/AZ, 1972-1973, No date (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Research Files -General -Undocumented Aliens, 1977-1980, No date (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Research Files -General -Unpublished Article Manuscripts, No date (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Research Files -General -Valasquez, 1989, No date (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Research Files -General -Vanishing Homelands, 1988-1992 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Research Files -General -Velvet Art, 1966-1999, No date (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Research Files -General -Vietnam and 60s/Bisbee, 1987, No date (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Research Files -General -Watergate, 1974-1999 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Research Files -General -What's Doing in San Salvador, No date (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - Research Files -General -Writers in Schools, 1985-1986, No date (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - Research Files -General -Writing, No date (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Research Files -General -Yaqui, No date (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Research Files -General -Yankees -New York, No date (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Research Files -General -Yuma/San Luis, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Subseries 2: Constitutional Calendar Research Files
    - Research Files -Constitutional Calendar -Correspondence, 1971-1980, No date (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -Constitutional Calendar -Miscellaneous Material (Pt.1), 1981-1987, No date (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -Constitutional Calendar -Miscellaneous Material (Pt.2), No date (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -Constitutional Calendar -Note Cards, No date (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 3: Guantanamo Bay Research Files
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Correspondence, 1972-1993, No date (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -A Few Good Men, 1989, No date (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Guantanamo Gazette (Incomplete), 1972-1990 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Guantanamo Bay Navel Base (Pt.1), 1964-1989 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Guantanamo Bay Navel Base (Pt.2), 1989-1990, No date (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Photographs (Includes Negitives), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Photographs and Postcards, No date (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Newspaper Clippings (Pt.1), 1959-1990 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Newspaper Clippings (Pt.2), 1991-1994, No date (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Miscellaneous Materials (Pt.1), 1932-1993 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Miscellaneous Materials (Pt.2), No date (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Raw Notes, Handwritten, No date (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Raw Notes, Index Cards, No date (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Raw Notes, Typed, 1991, No date (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Ronald W. Peterson Jr. Court Case Trial Copy, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -Guantanamo Bay -Tom Miller Articles, 1973, No date (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 4: Hanigan Case Research Files
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -Correspondence, 1979-1987, No date (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -Court Transcripts (Pt.1), 1976-1980s (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -Court Transcripts (Pt.2), 1976-1980s (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -Enlightened Nationals United for Freedom, 1979, No date (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -Hanigan Ranch Maps, No date (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -Miscellaneous Materials (Includes Photograph), 1976-1983, No date (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -National Coalition on the Hanigan Case: Correspondence, 1976-1980, No date (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Research Files -Hanigan Case -National Coalition on the Hanigan Case: Miscellaneous Materials (Pt.1), 1977-1979 (Box 43, Folder 1)